jewellerynetasia.com 2017-06-06

# Privacy Policy | JewelleryNetAsia - Global Network for Jewellery and Gem Professionals

This privacy policy explains how we handle your Personal and Business Data for our services. By visiting our Website and/or using our services, you both accept the Privacy Policy and explicitly consent to our collection, holding, storage, security, use and disclosure of your Personal and Business Data under the Personal Data (Privacy) Ordinance of Hong Kong.

**Collection of Information**  
When you visit the Website, we record your visit only as a 'hit' and do not collect any Personal and Business Data about you. The 'hit' records are to allow us to compile general statistics to show the number of visitors to the Website.  
Upon registration as a Supplier Member or Registered Visitor, we collect personal and business data from you. These Personal and Business Data will include information such as company name, contact persons, addresses, phone and fax numbers, email addresses, business nature, products of interest, together with other information which may be necessary or helpful to the provision of our services. Some of the Personal and Business Data is mandatory and some of it you may volunteer. If you do not wish to provide the mandatory fields at Personal and/or Business Data, we will be unable to register you as a Supplier Member or Registered Visitor.

We also collect Personal and Business Data from you before you use any services that we are providing, including but not limited to company information, product information, posting of trade leads and enquiry making, appointmentsetc. Again, if you do not wish to provide this Personal and Business Data, we may be unable to process your service usage request.

We also gather statistical information about the Website and Users including computer sign-on data, IP addresses, standard web log information, page views, traffic to and from the website, advertising data and more.

**Personal identity data collection [Visitors to Jewellery Exhibitions only]  
** In your pre-registrations to attend our [Jewellery exhibitions](http://www.jewellerynetasia.com/en/Fairs.html), passport/national identity card numbers and document scans may be collected for the prevention and detection of crime, and to protect the security and safety of our Jewellery exhibitions. Such data will be stored in our databases in order to verify your identity before, during and for a reasonable time after your visit to our Jewellery exhibitions. We do not use such data for any other purposes and will not share any such data to external parties unless required by law or any lawful request of any enforcement agencies. We will not be able to process your pre-registrations to our Jewellery exhibitions without the said identity support.

**Use of Information**  
We use your Personal and Business Data for the following purposes, including but not limited to:  
1.operate the Website and services;  
2.compile statistics on the use of the Website and services  
3.provide the services and customer support you request;  
4.improving and enhancing the features and services;  
5.process your service applications and requirements;  
6.contact you regarding notices, surveys, product alerts, new services, offers and communications relevant to you in which you may be interested;  
7.the additional purposes stated in the respective screens that invite you to provide such Personal and/or Business Data. 

**Disclosure of Information**  
We may disclose your Personal and Business Data to third parties, our partners and/or alliances, when:  
1\. we get your consent to share the information;  
2\. we need to share your information to provide the product or service you have requested;  
3\. required by subpoenas, court orders or legal process or in our opinion it is required to enable us to comply with any legal requirement of a law enforcement or governmental agency which has in our opinion relevant authorisation to obtain such information (when we may disclose the same without notification to you that we have done so);  
4.your activity on the Website violates our Terms of Services or any of our usage guidelines for specific products or services;  
5.we need to send your information to merchants, payment processing service providers and financial institutions for the purposes set out above.

**Co-branded and alliance relationship**  
We have established relationships with other parties to offer you the benefit of other products and services which we ourselvesmay not offer. We offer you access to these other parties either through the use of hyperlinks to their sites from our Website, or through offering "co-branded" sites in which both these other parties and ourselves share the same URL, domain name or pages within a domain name on the Internet. Generally, we do not own the co-branded and alliance parties. It is, therefore, important that you understand their privacy policy and/or terms of use if you visit and use their sites.

**Retention**  
Our general policy is to retain records of your visits and online dealings without time limitation.

**Cookies**  
When you browse the Website, cookies may be stored in your computer's hard drive. We use cookies to personalise your use of the Website and to operate the service areas. You have a choice not to accept cookies, but if you do certain functionality may not be available.

**Security Measures**  
We employ commercially reasonable security methods to prevent unauthorised access, maintain data accuracy and ensure correct use of information. However, we are unable to ensure that all your Personal and Business Data will never be disclosed or used in ways contrary to this Privacy Policy and are not liable in such circumstances.

In general, your Personal and Business Data is kept confidential and is only accessible by authorised personnel. We recommend that you do not divulge your User Login Name and Password to anyone. Our personnel will never ask you for your User Login Name and Password in an unsolicited phone call or in an unsolicited e-mail. Remember to sign out of your Account and close your browser window when you have finished your session with the Website. You are responsible for all activities that occur under your User Account and Password.

**Disclaimers**  
No data transmission over the Internet or any wireless network can be guaranteed to be perfectly secured. As a result, while we try to protect your information, we cannot ensure or guarantee the security of any information you transmit to us and you do so at your own risk.

The Website may include links to external sites, including sites of members, third parties and "co-branded" sites. Links to external sites do not imply any endorsement of such sites (or any products or services offered thereon) by us or any warranty or guarantee of any information provided thereon. We disclaim and exclude any responsibility or liability for any external site for which a link is provided and this Privacy Policy shall not apply to any such site.

**Changes to privacy policy**  
Any changes to this Privacy Policy Statement will be postedon this webpageand effective immediately on the posting date.

You agree to indemnify UBM Asia and all Related Persons from and against all Claims arising out of your use of this Website or the use of this Website by any person using your User Account, your password and/or your Personal and Business Data. If there is any conflict between the Chinese and English versions of this Statement, the English version prevails.
